var questions = [{
	"question": " What is the meaning of Pakistan?",
	"option1": "Holy Land",
	"option2": "Desert",
	"option3": "Land of five rivers",
	"option4": "Unity",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "What is the capital city of Pakistan?",
	"option1": "Karachi ",
	"option2": "Islamabad",
	"option3": "Lahore",
	"option4": "Punjab",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": " Who was the first Governor General of Pakistan?",
	"option1": "Muhammad Ali Jinnah",
	"option2": "Liaquat Ali Khan",
	"option3": "Ayub Khan",
	"option4": "Sikandar Mirza",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Where is Quaid -e- Azam's Tomb?",
	"option1": "Islamabad",
	"option2": "Quetta",
	"option3": "Lahore",
	"option4": "Karachi",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "Which is the national flower of Pakistan? ?",
	"option1": "Rose",
	"option2": "Tulips",
	"option3": "Jasmine",
	"option4": "Camomille",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Which is the national language of Pakistan?",
	"option1": "Hindi",
	"option2": "Urdu",
	"option3": "English",
	"option4": "Bengali",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Which is the national bird of Pakistan?",
	"option1": "Eagle",
	"option2": "Crow",
	"option3": "Chakor",
	"option4": "Peacock",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "How many letters are there in Urdu alphabets:?",
	"option1": "35",
	"option2": "36",
	"option3": "37",
	"option4": "39",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Who composed the verses of Pakistan national Anthem?",
	"option1": "Hafeez Jallandri",
	"option2": "Nasir",
	"option3": "Allama Iqbal",
	"option4": "Faiz Ahmed Faiz",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Which is the tallest building in Pakistan?",
	"option1": "MCB",
	"option2": "Habib Bank Plaza",
	"option3": "Bahria Icon Tower ",
	"option4": "UBL",
	"answer": "3"
}];